<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.dynatrace.wizard</id>
    <name>Dynatrace Mobile Wizard</name>
    <vendor email="android-support@dynatrace.com" url="https://www.dynatrace.com">Dynatrace</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        <p>
            <b>Dynatrace Mobile Wizard</b> is a guided setup tool for Android developers that automatically
            configures the <b>Dynatrace OneAgent Mobile SDK</b> in your project — no manual Gradle editing required.
        </p>
        <p>
            Open it from <b>Tools → Dynatrace Wizard…</b>, right-click in the editor, or right-click in
            the Project view. The wizard detects your project structure and walks you through every step.
        </p>

        <h3>What it does</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Project detection</b> — identifies Gradle DSL (Kotlin or Groovy), module layout,
                existing Dynatrace configuration, and the optimal plugin approach
                (Plugin DSL vs buildscript classpath)</li>
            <li><b>Multi-module support</b> — single-app, multi-app, and dynamic feature module projects;
                per-module Application ID and Beacon URL; optional OneAgent SDK for library modules</li>
            <li><b>Environment setup</b> — validates Application ID and Beacon URL with inline feedback</li>
            <li><b>Technology overview</b> — shows which Dynatrace monitoring capabilities apply to your stack</li>
            <li><b>Full feature control</b> — toggles for crash reporting, user actions, web request monitoring,
                Jetpack Compose instrumentation, hybrid (WebView) monitoring, location, privacy,
                rage-tap detection, build-variant targeting, class/method exclusions, and more</li>
            <li><b>Change preview</b> — shows the exact Gradle code that will be written before you commit</li>
            <li><b>Safe writes</b> — every file edit uses <code>WriteCommandAction</code>, making all
                changes fully undoable via <b>Edit → Undo</b></li>
        </ul>

        <h3>Wizard tabs</h3>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Welcome</b> — detects Android project, DSL, module structure, and setup flow</li>
            <li><b>Modules</b> — select which app modules to instrument; configure approach for multi-app projects</li>
            <li><b>Environment</b> — enter Application ID and Beacon URL (per-module for multi-app)</li>
            <li><b>Technologies</b> — supported technology overview for your project's dependencies</li>
            <li><b>Features</b> — enable/disable individual instrumentation capabilities</li>
            <li><b>Skills</b> — export a reusable Markdown <code>skills.md</code> for AI coding agents</li>
            <li><b>Summary</b> — full Gradle code preview; click Finish to apply</li>
        </ol>

        <h3>Supported project types</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>Single-module Android apps</li>
            <li>Multi-module projects (app + library + dynamic feature modules)</li>
            <li>Kotlin DSL (<code>build.gradle.kts</code>) and Groovy DSL (<code>build.gradle</code>)</li>
            <li>Plugin DSL (<code>plugins {}</code>) and legacy buildscript classpath approach</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>Requirements</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1+ or Android Studio Koala+</li>
            <li>An Android project with at least one <code>com.android.application</code> module</li>
            <li>A Dynatrace account with a configured Mobile application (Application ID + Beacon URL)</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <notificationGroup id="Dynatrace Wizard"
                           displayType="BALLOON"
                           toolWindowId="Event Log"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="com.dynatrace.wizard.DynatraceWizardAction"
                class="com.dynatrace.wizard.DynatraceWizardAction"
                text="Dynatrace Wizard…"
                description="Open the Dynatrace Mobile SDK configuration wizard">
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>
